Finding Aid for William G. Milliken papers 1961-1982
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Administrative / Executive Files
  - Staff Files, 224 linear feet
    - Phil Kazmierski/Tom Drake 1974-1982
      - Agriculture
        - Michigan Department of Agriculture
          - Agriculture Land Preservation, 1975-82 (Box 739)
          - Agriculture Land Protection Act (H.R. 2551), 1979-82 (Box 739)
          - Animal Health 1981 (Box 739)
          - Budget, 1981-82 (Box 739)
          - Cargo Diversion 1982 (Box 739)
          - Climate Program, 1978-79 (Box 739)
          - Conference on Agriculture, 1980-82 (Box 739)
          - Curene 442, 1979-81 (Box 739)
          - Development Revenue Bonds 1980 (Box 739)
          - Districting Legislation 1980 (Box 739)
          - Drains, 1979-80 (Box 739)
          - Exports/Agricultural Products 1982 (Box 739)
          - Federal Affairs and Issues, 1979-80 (Box 739)
          - Food and Dairy/Weights and Measures 1981 (Box 739)
          - Food Inspection 1980 (Box 739)
          - Fonofos 1981 (Box 739)
          - Frozen Desserts, 1979-80 (Box 739)
          - Gasohol. 1979-80 (Box 739)
          - Gleaning 1979 (Box 739)
          - Grain Embargo 1980 (Box 739)
          - Growth Conference (801) 1980 (Box 739)
          - Horses 1979-1982, 5 folders (Box 739)
          - Inheritance Tax/USDA Estate Tax, 1978-79 (Box 739)
          - Insect Problem/Gypsy Moth 1975-1982 (Box 740)
          - International Trade, 1979-81 (Box 740)
          - Invitations, 1979-80 (Box 740)
          - Job Development 1979 (Box 740)
          - Meat Inspection, 1975-81 (Box 740)
          - National Agriculture Bargaining Act, 1979-82 (Box 740)
          - PBB 1979-1982 (Box 740)
          - PCB 1978-1981 (Box 740)
          - PCP 1979-1980 (Box 740)
          - Regulations 1978-1979 (Box 740)
          - Research Stations 1979-1981, 2 folders (Box 740)
          - Scrapie 1980-1981 (Box 740)
          - Soil Conservation 1981 (Box 740)
          - Travel Report 1979 (Box 740)
        - U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1981-82 (Box 740)
      - Education
        - Alpena Public Schools, 1981-82 (Box 740)
        - Ann Arbor
          - Black English Case 1979 (Box 740)
          - Teaching-Learning Communities (Tice) 1979 (Box 740)
        - Appointment Recommendations, 1980-81 (Box 740)
        - Associations/Councils/Organizations
          - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities of Michigan (AICUM) 1980 (Box 740)
          - Education Commission of the States (ECS)
            - General (Box 740)
            - Meetings 1979-1981, 3 folders (Box 740)
          - Education Council of Michigan 1977-1980, 2 folders (Box 740)
          - Huron Valley Advisory Council 1981-1982 (Box 740)
          - Michigan Association for the Academically Talented 1980 (Box 741)
          - Michigan Association of Educational Options, 1980-81 (Box 741)
          - Michigan Association of School Administrators (MASA), 1979-82 (Box 741)
          - Michigan Association of School Boards (MASB) 1981 (Box 741)
          - Michigan Community College Association, 1980-82 (Box 741)
          - Michigan Education Association (MEA)
            - General, 1978-82 (Box 741)
            - Endorsement of WGM June 1978 (Box 741)
          - Michigan Federation of Teachers (Detroit), 1981-82 (Box 741)
          - National Association of State Boards of Education (NASBE) 1980 (Box 741)
          - Parent-Teacher Association (PTA) 1980 (Box 741)
          - Presidents Council of State Colleges and Universities 1980 (Box 741)
        - Attorney General 1980-1982, 2 folders (Box 741)
        - "A" Miscellaneous Correspondence 1981 (Box 741)
        - Baake Case (Reverse Discrimination), 1977-78 (Box 741)
        - Benton Harbor School District-Desegregation Case, 1980-81, 2 folders (Box 741)
        - Budget, 1980-81, 2 folders (Box 741)
        - "B" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1980-81 (Box 741)
        - Cadillac School Board Recall 1981 (Box 741)
        - Children's Center for Social Change 1980 (Box 741)
        - Collective and Regional Bargaining 1979 (Box 741)
        - Connection Task Force 1981 (Box 741)
        - "C" Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 741)
        - Detroit Public Schools
          - General, 1974-82, 2 folders (Box 741)
          - Decentralization 1978-1982, 3 folders (Box 741)
          - Desegregation
            - General, 1979-81 (Box 741)
            - Bradley Supreme Court Decision, 1977-81 (Box 741)
          - United States District Court Monitoring Commission 1982 (Box 741)
        - East Jackson Public Schools vs. State Board of Education 1982 (Box 742)
        - Economic Development/Diversification, 1980-82 (Box 742)
        - Education: State
          - Alternative Education, Proposals for Federal Funding of1979-80 (Box 742)
          - Alternate Uses of School Buildings, 1979-80 (Box 742)
          - Block Grant Advisory Committee for Education 1982 (Box 742)
          - Citizens Task Force on Education 1980 (Box 742)
          - Community and Adult Education
            - General 1981-82 (Box 742)
            - Adult Education Funding Task Force 1981 (Box 742)
            - "The History of Public School Adult Education in Michigan 1862-1977 (Box 742)
          - Conversion of School Building to Senior Citizen Housing 1980 (Box 742)
          - Department of Education
            - General, 1980-82 (Box 742)
            - Budget 1979-1982, 3 folders (Box 742)
            - Hiring Freeze Exemptions, 1979-81 (Box 742)
            - Project Close-Up 1981 (Box 742)
            - Project Outreach, 1981-82 (Box 742)
            - Vocational Rehabilitation 1980 (Box 742)
          - Desegregation-Busing, 1979-82 (Box 742)
          - Emergency Rules 1981, 2 folders (Box 742)
          - Environmental Education, 1977-78 (Box 742)
          - General Laws/Administrative Rules 1981 (Box 742)
          - Global Education 1981 (Box 742)
          - Office of Preprimary and Family Education, 1979-81, 2 folders (Box 742)
          - State Board of Education
            - General 1982 (Box 742)
            - Commission on the High School 1982 (Box 742)
            - Printed Material, 1977-82 (Box 742)
          - State Tenure Commission 1980 (Box 742)
          - Teenage Parent Program (Box 742)
        - Education: Federal
          - General, 1980-82 (Box 743)
          - Budget 1980 (Box 743)
          - Budget Cuts 1981 (Box 743)
          - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act of 1978 (CETA), 1978-81 (Box 743)
          - President's Youth Initiative 1980 (Box 743)
        - Education-Elementary/Secondary
          - Assessment Testing, 1978-82 (Box 743)
          - Bilingual, 1980-82 (Box 743)
          - CPR Training in Public Schools 1979 (Box 743)
          - Centralized School Bus Purchasing, 1979-80 (Box 743)
          - Class Size 1979 (Box 743)
          - Consolidation of K-12 Districts, 1980-82 (Box 743)
          - Declining Enrollments, 1977-80 (Box 743)
          - Driver's Education, 1980-81 (Box 743)
          - Gifted and Talented Programs, 3 folders (Box 743)
          - Intermediate School District Reorganization, 1979-81, 3 folders (Box 743)
          - Parochial Schools, 1979-80 (Box 743)
          - Rayla Elementary School (Scrapbook) 1970 (Box 743)
          - Regional Educational Media Centers (REMC'S) (Box 743)
          - Science and Math (Box 743)
          - Secondary Reading and Support Materials (Box 743)
          - Sex Education 1980 (Box 743)
          - Special Education, 1980-82 (Box 744)
          - Vocational Education 1979-1982, 3 folders (Box 744)
          - Work-Education Councils 1979, 2 folders (Box 744)
        - Education: Higher Education
          - Capital Investment Committee 1979-1980 (Box 744)
          - Community Colleges, 1979-81 (Box 744)
          - Department of Transportation Awards to Academic Institutions 1981 (Box 744)
          - Governance, 1980-81 (Box 744)
          - Higher Education Commission 1982 (Box 744)
          - Higher Education Coordination 1980 (Box 744)
          - Indian Tuition Waiver Program, 1979-81 (Box 744)
          - Michigan Medical School Council, Fifth Pathway Program, 1978-80 (Box 744)
          - Midwest Regional Concept to Higher Education, 1976-78 (Box 744)
          - Professional Development 1979-1982, 2 folders (Box 744)
          - Regional Conferences 1980 (Box 744)
          - Science and Technology, 1980-82 (Box 744)
          - Student Financial Assistance
            - General, 1980-82 (Box 744)
            - Guaranteed Student Loans 1981 (Box 744)
            - Tax Credits for Tuition 1978 (Box 744)
          - Tuition Reciprocity-Eastern Michigan University/University of Toledo 1982 (Box 744)
          - Miscellaneous, 1979-81, 2 folders (Box 744)
        - Employment-Trade Readjustment Act 1981 (Box 745)
        - Federal Legislation
          - General, 1979-81 (Box 745)
          - Urban Grant University Act (H.R. 7328) 1978 (Box 745)
        - Freedom of Information 1979 (Box 745)
        - Gallop Polls on Attitudes Toward Education (Box 745)
        - Grand Rapids School District 1980 (Box 745)
        - Grand Valley State Colleges 1981 (Box 745)
        - Great Lakes Maritime Academy, 1979-82 (Box 745)
        - Halick, John (Dr.) 1981 (Box 745)
        - Handicapper Affairs, 1980-82 (Box 745)
        - Hartley Outdoor Education Center (Outdoor Education Manual) (Box 745)
        - Headlee Amendment Implementation 1979 (Box 745)
        - Human Services Cabinet 1980 (Box 745)
        - "H" Miscellaneous Correspondence 1981 (Box 745)
        - Juvenile Code 1981 (Box 745)
        - Kalamazoo Desegregation Case 1981 (Box 745)
        - Lansing Community College, 1980-82 (Box 745)
        - Legal Database (Box 745)
        - Legislation
          - General, 1980-82 (Box 745)
          - Amendment to School Code-re: Expulsion 1981 (Box 745)
          - Department of Education (Review) 1979 (Box 745)
          - Due Process, (H.B. 4398) (Box 745)
          - Federal Legislation 1980 (Box 745)
          - Open Meetings Act 1981 (Box 745)
        - Libraries
          - General, 1979-82 (Box 745)
          - Detroit Public Library (Box 745)
          - State Law Library, 1980-81 (Box 745)
          - State Library, 1978-82, 2 folders (Box 745)
        - Lobbying Rules 1978 (Box 745)
        - Management and Budget, 1980-82 (Box 745)
        - Metric Commission 1979 (Box 745)
        - Michigan Corporation of Public Broadcasting 1981 (Box 745)
        - Michigan Higher Education Assistance Authority/Michigan Higher Education Student Loan Authority, 1980-82 (Box 745)
        - Michigan Higher Education Facilities Commission, 1978-81 (Box 745)
        - Michigan School for the Blind, 1978-82 (Box 746)
        - Michigan State University, 1980-82 (Box 746)
        - Michigan Technological University 1980 (Box 746)
        - Milliken, Governor, 1980-82 (Box 746)
        - National Governor's Association 1980-1982 (Box 746)
        - National Institute for Burn Medicine, 1980-82 (Box 746)
        - National Institute of Education (NIE) 1980-1981, 4 folders (Box 746)
        - National Youth Science Camp, 1976-82 (Box 746)
        - Neighborhood Education Authority 1978 (Box 746)
        - Northern Michigan University, 1980-82 (Box 746)
        - Nutrition-Child Care Food Program, 1980-81 (Box 746)
        - Oakland University, 1980-81 (Box 746)
        - Owendale-Gagetown School District, 1976-82 (Box 746)
        - Pontiac Schools, 1980=82 (Box 746)
        - Property Tax
          - General 1980 (Box 746)
          - Property Tax Alternatives 1980 (Box 746)
          - Proposals 1976-1981, 4 folders (Box 746)
          - Summer Tax Collections (Box 746)
          - Tax Reform 1981 (Box 746)
          - Tax Relief, 1978-80 (Box 746)
          - Tax Revision Task Force in School Finance Research Group 1976 (Box 746)
        - Publicom-Special Education Task Force 1980 (Box 746)
        - Religious Practices in the Schools (Box 746)
        - Retirement 1977, 4 folders (Box 747)
        - "R" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1981-82 (Box 747)
        - Sadat, Madame Anwar-Visit to Michigan (Box 747)
        - Saginaw Central Junior High School, 1974-80 (Box 747)
        - School District Consolidation (Crestwood, Dearborn Heights, Westwood) 1982 (Box 747)
        - School Finance
          - General, 1980-82, 2 folders (Box 747)
          - Budget 1978-1982, 2 folders (Box 747)
          - Bursley Bill (Second Year Analysis) (Box 747)
          - "Circuit Breaker" Article for Michigan Association of School Boards Magazine (Box 747)
          - Districts with Financial Difficulty, 1981-82 (Box 747)
          - Governor's Income Tax Option 1978 (Box 747)
          - Municipal Overburden Funding 1979 (Box 747)
          - New York School Finance Decision, Implications 1981 (Box 747)
          - Pooling Loan Issues Against State Aid (Box 747)
          - "Results of the Governor's School Finance Survey" by James Phelps (Box 747)
          - Voucher Funding, 1977-78, 2 folders (Box 747)
        - School Vandalism and Violence, 1978-81 (Box 747)
        - Sex Education in Schools, 1977-81 (Box 747)
        - Sex Equity
          - General, 1980-82 (Box 747)
          - On Site Planning (OSP Model) 1981-1982 (Box 747)
          - Superintendent's Study Group 1980 (Box 747)
        - Strikes (Teacher's)
          - Legislation, 1980-83 (Box 747)
          - Southgate District 1980-1982, 2 folders (Box 747)
        - Taylor Public Schools, 1981-82 (Box 748)
        - Telecommunications 1981 (Box 748)
        - Tenure Commission 1982 (Box 748)
        - Transportation (School Buses for Public Transportation) 1982 (Box 748)
        - University of Michigan, 1980-82 (Box 748)
        - Wayne County Community College, 1978-82 (Box 748)
        - Wayne State University, 1980-82 (Box 748)
        - Wayne-Westland School District
          - General 1982 (Box 748)
          - School Proposal for Joint Funding 1980 (Box 748)
        - White House Conference on Families for 1980, 2 folders (Box 748)
        - Youth Employment
          - CETA, 1981-82 (Box 748)
          - Jobs for America's Graduates (JAG) Program, 1981-82 (Box 748)
          - Leadership Conference, 1980-81 (Box 748)
      - Legislative Liaison
        - Legislation
          - General, 1981-82 (Box 748)
          - Agriculture, Prompt Pay Legislation (S.B. 111, 113, 338) 1981 (Box 748)
          - Legalized Raffles, 1981-82 (Box 748)
          - Mental Health Code Amendment (H.B. 4554) 1982 (Box 748)
          - Minority Business Development, Public Act 428 1980 (Box 748)
          - School Violence and Vandalism (H.B. 4398) Student Code of Conduct 1981 (Box 748)
          - Single Business Tax. 1982 (Box 748)
        - Legislation-Federal, Farm Bill 1981 (Box 748)
        - Legislative
          - General 1981 (Box 748)
          - Law, Robert C. (Legislative Issue Memos) (Box 748)
          - Leadership 1982 (Box 748)
      - Transportation
        - General 1978-1982 (Box 748)
        - Aeronautics/Airline/Aviation
          - Aeronautics, 1980-82, 3 folders (Box 748)
          - Airlines, 1981-81 (Box 748)
          - Committee Airlines, 1978-82, 2 folders (Box 748)
          - Deregulation, 1979-81 (Box 748)
          - Freedom Airlines, 1980-82 (Box 748)
          - King Air, 1979-80 (Box 748)
          - Low Level Flights, 1980-81 (Box 748)
          - United Airlines Reduction, 1979-80 (Box 748)
        - Affirmative Action, 1977-81 (Box 749)
        - Budget 1979-1981, 2 folders (Box 749)
        - Bridges 1982 (Box 749)
        - Bus Transit
          - General, 1978-82 (Box 749)
          - Hi Way American 1976 (Box 749)
          - Intercity Bus 1978-1982 (Box 749)
        - Community Development 1980-1981 (Box 749)
        - Comprehensive Transportation Fund 1981 (Box 749)
        - Coordination/Consolidation Transportation Services 1980-1981, 5 folders (Box 749)
        - Detroit
          - General 1981 (Box 749)
          - Downtown People Mover Project (DPM), 1978-79 (Box 749)
          - Plant Project 1980 (Box 749)
        - Drunk Driving 1982 (Box 749)
        - Energy Issues/Fuels
          - Diesel Tax, 1980-81 (Box 749)
          - Gas Tax Bill 1978 (Box 749)
        - Federal Transportation Issues, 1979-82 (Box 749)
        - Funding-Transportation, 1980-82 (Box 749)
        - Handicapper Concerns, 1981-82 (Box 749)
        - Highways
          - General, 1981-82 (Box 749)
          - A Ten Year Highway Program for Michigan, 1970-80 (Box 749)
          - I-69, 1980-81 (Box 749)
          - I-696 1980 (Box 749)
          - M-53, 1979-81 (Box 749)
          - M-275, 1979-80 (Box 749)
          - Highway Beautification, 1979-80 (Box 749)
          - Highway Safety 1980-1981, 2 folders (Box 749)
          - Highway Signing 1979 (Box 749)
          - Local Roads 1979 (Box 749)
          - State Enforcement of National Maximum Speed Limit 1981 (Box 749)
          - Trucking Issues
            - Double Bottom Tankers 1981 (Box 749)
            - Size and Weight Laws and Regulations/Interstate System 1982 (Box 749)
            - Truck Size and Weight Enforcement in Detroit, 1981-82 (Box 749)
            - Truck Spillage (Box 749)
            - Truck Weights, 1979-80 (Box 749)
            - Trunklines, 4 folders (Box 749)
        - Legislation
          - Clean Air (Re: Vehicle Emissions), 1980-82 (Box 750)
          - Federal 1982 (Box 750)
          - Helmet Law, 1979-81 (Box 750)
          - Moped Legislation 1982 (Box 750)
          - Seat Belt Use Law, 1981-82, 2 folders (Box 750)
          - State, 1979-82 (Box 750)
          - Transportation Funding, 1981-82 (Box 750)
          - Transportation Package 1981 (Box 750)
          - Urban Enterprise Zone Act 1981 (Box 750)
        - Motorcycle Registration Fee, 1979-82 (Box 750)
        - National Governors' Conference, 1981-82 (Box 750)
        - Railroads
          - General, 1981-82 (Box 750)
          - Administrative Rules/Interstate Rates 1982 (Box 750)
          - Chessie System Railroad 1982 (Box 750)
          - Conrail 1982 (Box 750)
          - Escanaba and Lake Superior Railroad 1982 (Box 750)
          - Freight-Rail, 1981-82, 4 folders (Box 750)
          - Grand Trunk Western Railroad Company 1982 (Box 750)
          - Magner-O'Hara Scenic Railway 1980 (Box 750)
          - Mass Transit Systems 1980, 2 folders (Box 750)
          - Michigan Interstate Railroad (old Ann Arbor Railroad) 1982 (Box 750)
          - Michigan Northern Railroad 1982 (Box 750)
          - Michigan-Ontario/Memo of Understanding 1981 (Box 750)
          - Michigan Railroad Laws 1982 (Box 750)
          - Passenger (Rail) 1979-1982, 2 folders (Box 750)
          - Penn Central Railroad 1981 (Box 750)
          - Rail Safety (Box 750)
          - Transporting Hazardous Materials 1981 (Box 750)
          - Tuscola and Saginaw Bay Railway Funding Application 1981 (Box 750)
        - Reindustrialization Related Transportation Needs and Issues 1981, 2 folders (Box 750)
        - Senior Citizen and Handicapper Ridership 1981 (Box 750)
        - Silverdome Transportation Flow Improvements (Box 750)
        - Southeast Michigan Transportation Authority
          - Merger with Detroit, Department of Transportation, 1978-82, 3 folders (Box 751)
          - Plan, 1979-81, 3 folders (Box 751)
          - Tax 1980 (Box 751)
        - State of the State 1977, 1979, 4 folders (Box 751)
        - Transportation, Department of
          - General, 1981-82 (Box 751)
          - Department Reorganization 1979 (Box 751)
          - Transportation Commission, 1979-81 (Box 751)
        - Transportation Needs Study 1982 (Box 752)
        - Transportation Package 1977-1979, 4 folders (Box 752)
        - Transportation Systems Management (ISM) 1982 (Box 752)
        - Upper Peninsula Conference 1979 (Box 752)
        - United States Army Corps of Engineers 1982 (Box 752)
        - United States Coast Guard 1982 (Box 752)
        - Uptran, 1979-82, 2 folders (Box 752)
        - Water Transportation
          - General 1979 (Box 752)
          - Cross Lake Auto/Passenger Service, 1981-82 (Box 752)
          - Ferry, 1979-82, 2 folders (Box 752)
          - Great Lakes Commission/Icebreaker-"Mackinaw" 1982 (Box 752)
          - Port Council, 1980-81 (Box 752)
          - Ports, 1981-82 (Box 752)
          - Tug/Barge, 1979-82, 2 folders (Box 752)
      - Miscellaneous Files
        - Abortion 1982 (Box 753)
        - Appointments/Recommendations for 1982 (Box 753)
        - Attorney General's Opinions (Box 753)
        - Budget 1982 (Box 753)
        - Commerce, Department of/Insurance Bureau Accident Fund 1982 (Box 753)
        - Community Development 1980 (Box 753)
        - Community Placement 1981 (Box 753)
        - Economic Development, 1981-82 (Box 753)
        - Economic Recovery, 1981-82 (Box 753)
        - Executive Office Staff Correspondence, 1981-82 (Box 753)
        - Federal Affairs, 1980-81 (Box 753)
        - Federal Excise Taxes 1982 (Box 753)
        - "G" Miscellaneous Correspondence 1981 (Box 753)
        - Hiring Freeze 1981 (Box 753)
        - "H" Miscellaneous Correspondence 1982 (Box 753)
        - Issues Book 1976 (Box 753)
        - Issues Summary 1978 (Box 753)
        - "J" Miscellaneous Correspondence 1982 (Box 753)
        - Milliken, William G. Governor, 1981-82 (Box 753)
        - National Governors' Association, 1980-82 (Box 753)
        - "O" Miscellaneous Correspondence 1981 (Box 753)
        - Paperwork Resolution 1982 (Box 753)
        - "P" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1981-82 (Box 753)
        - Regulatory Review, 1981-82, 2 folders (Box 753)
        - Social Services (Workfare Programs) 1982 (Box 753)
        - Speeches, Drafts for Governor 1981 (Box 753)
        - State Affairs 1977 (Box 753)
        - State of State, 1981-82, 3 folders (Box 753)
        - Unemployment Insurance 1982 (Box 753)
        - Upper Peninsula Conference, 1980-81 (Box 753)
        - Upper Peninsula State Affairs Visit, Briefing Book 1978 (Box 753)
        - "T"-"U" Miscellaneous Correspondence 1982 (Box 753)
        - Vetoes 1982 (Box 753)
        - Workers Compensation 1982 (Box 753)
        - "V"-"W" Miscellaneous Correspondence 1982 (Box 753)
    - James Kellogg/Mark Mason
      - Administrative Files
        - Issue Briefings 1971 (Box 754)
        - General Departmental Communications 1969-1973 (Box 754)
        - Governor Milliken
          - State of the State 1972-1973, 2 folders (Box 754)
          - Special Messages (Miscellaneous) (Box 754)
          - Speech Materials (Background), 2 folders (Box 754)
      - Correspondence
        - General 1973-1974, 2 folders (Box 754)
        - Chamberlain, Representative Charles E (Box 754)
        - Ford, Representative Gerald R (Box 754)
        - Griffiths, Representative Martha W (Box 754)
        - Harvey, Representative James (Box 754)
        - Huber, Robert J.(18th District) (Box 754)
        - McDonald, Representative Jack H (Box 754)
      - Memoranda (Staff) (Box 754)
      - Environment
        - Air Pollution, 1970-72, 3 folders (Box 754)
        - Alewives (Box 754)
        - Auto Pollution, 1972-73 (Box 754)
        - Bottles and Cans Issue (Correspondence) (Box 754)
        - Clean Earth Corps (Box 754)
        - Coho Disposal (Box 754)
        - Commercial Fishing, 1971-72 (Box 754)
        - Comprehensive Health Planning (Urban) (Box 754)
        - Conner's Creek Marina (Box 754)
        - Conservation (Ft. Custer Land and Kalamazoo and Battle Creek Facility) (Box 754)
        - Corps of Engineers (Box 754)
        - 1972-73 General (Box 754)
        - Correspondence (Box 754)
        - Council of State Government (Special Report) (Box 755)
        - Coyote Bounty (Box 755)
        - Detergents and Phosphates (Box 755)